Guide to the Department of Zoology records, 1873-1965.
Department of Zoology records
- Series II. Correspondence
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1948-1949
    - University Library Board, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - University Testing Service, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Van Cleef Memorial Library, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Veterans Education Office, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Veterinary Curriculum, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Von Frisch, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - W, correspondents by last name, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Ward's Natural Science Establishment, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Will Corporation, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1949-1950
    - A, correspondents by last name, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Assistantships, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Assistantships Continued, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Applications to the Department of Zoology, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - B, correspondents by last name, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - C, correspondents by last name, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Committee on Language, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Committee on University Policy, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - D, correspondents by last name, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Daniels, Whitman, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Dean, Office of the, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Dean, Office of the, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Degree Candidates, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Department Staff Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Department Fire, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Department Annual Inventory, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Department of Zoology, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Department of Buildings and Grounds, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - F, correspondents by last name, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - G, correspondents by last name, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Graduate School, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Graduate School Admittances, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Graduate School Student Records, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Graduate School Candidates, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Greater Cornell Fund, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Griffin, Donald R., 1948-1950 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Heinicke Instruments Corporation, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - I, correspondents by last name, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Inside Cornell, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - J, correspondents by last name, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - K, correspondents by last name, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - L, correspondents by last name, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Library Associates, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Meeting-Eastern Colleges Science Conference, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Mueller, R. M., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - N, correspondents by last name, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - P, correspondents by last name, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Phi Kappa Phi, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Placement Bureau, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Positions at other institutions, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - President, Office of the, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Purchasing Department, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - R, correspondents by last name, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Recommendation, Letters of, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Respiration Equipment, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Reynolds, Victor, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Science Service, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Sigma Xi, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Statler Club, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Summer Session, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Swanson, Gustav A., 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - T, correspondents by last name, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Telephone Numbers, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - University Library, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - University Library Board, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - University Registrar's Office, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - University Testing Service, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - University Treasurer's Office, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Veterans Education, Office of, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Veterinary College, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - W, correspondents by last name, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Ward's Natural Science Establishment, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Y, correspondents by last name, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1950-1951
    - Assistantships, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Advisory System, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Anslow Jr., W. Parker, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Assistantships cont., 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Assistantships cont., 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Applications for Department Positions, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Army Medical Library, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Arcay, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - B, correspondents by last name, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Babcock, Howard E., 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Book and Supply Report, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 100)
      Contains blueprints of Stimson Hall
    - Buildings and Grounds cont., 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - C, correspondents by last name, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Committee on University Policy, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Candidates for Professorship, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Courses in Electrical Engineering, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - D, correspondents by last name, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Dean, Office of the, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Documents, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Department of Purchasing, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Department Staff Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Department Inventory, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - Department Seminars, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - De Wilde, Henry, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Directory of Staff, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - E, correspondents by last name, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Entomology Department, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Frisch, Karl von, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Felines and other animals for sale, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Fulbright Opportunities, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Fulton, John F., 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - G, correspondents by last name, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Graduate School, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Graduate Student Information, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Graduate School Applicants, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Graduate Allotment, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Heinicke Instrument Corporation, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Honors Program, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - I, correspondents by last name, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - J, correspondents by last name, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - K, correspondents by last name, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Library Board, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Library Associates, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Medical School, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Newspaper clipping
    - Medicine, School of, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Military Affairs, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - N, correspondents by last name, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - P, correspondents by last name, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Personnel Department, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Personnel Office, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Positions at other institutions, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Postings of Graduate Assistantships, Fellowships, and Scholarships, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - President, Office of the, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - President, Acting, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Purchasing Department, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - R, correspondents by last name, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Recommendations, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Reconstruction - Buildings and Grounds, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Seaman, Arlene R., 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Secretary, Office of the, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Social Security, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Society, Phi Beta Kappa, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Society, Phi Kappa Phi, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Society, Sigma Xi, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Student Organization of ILR, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Summer Research, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Summer Session, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - T, correspondents by last name, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Testing, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Technical Employees' Work Schedule, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - V, correspondents by last name, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Veterans Education, Office of, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Veterinary College, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - W, correspondents by last name, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Ward's Natural Science Establishment, Inc., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Will Corporation, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Wright, T. P., 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Zoology, Department of, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1951-1952
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences' Convention, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Air Raid Drills, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Applications, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Assistantship, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - B, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Bausch and Lomb Optical Co., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - C, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Committee on University Policy, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - D, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Dean, Office of the, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Department General Order, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Department Staff Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Department of Zoology Seminars, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - E, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - F, G, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Graduate School, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Graduate Faculty, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Graduate Student Information, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Graduate Admissions, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Griffin, Donald R., 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - I, J, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - K, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Kent, John F., 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - L, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Laboratory Animals, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Leonard, Samuel L., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Matheson, Robert, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Medical Education, Journal of, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Military Service, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Montagna, William A., 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Multiplex, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - N, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - O, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Organizations, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - P, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Parmenter, Richard, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Platt, Dorothy Bella Berner, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Positions at other institutions, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - President, Office of the, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Purchasing Department, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - R, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Research Position, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Reichmann, Felix, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Repairs, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Remodeling in Stimson Hall, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - Research - Corporations and Higher Education, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - Research Grant, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - Rossiter Report, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - Rulloff, Edward, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 111)
      Contains newspaper clippings on the story of Edward Rulloff
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Science, American Association for the Advance of, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Seaman, Arlene, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Society, Phi Beta Kappa, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Society, Phi Kappa Phi, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Society, Sigma Xi, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Service, Internal Revenue, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Summer Session, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - T, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - University Archives, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - University Directory, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - University Library, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - V, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Vice President, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - W, correspondents by last name, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Ward's Natural Science Establishment, Inc., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - Will Corporation, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - Willers, Diedrich K., 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Wright, T. P., 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1952-1953
    - A, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Anderson, John M., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - Applications, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Applications cont., 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Archives, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - B, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - C, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - D, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - Dean, Office of the, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Dominion Civil Service Fellowship, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - Department General Order, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Department Staff Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Department Chairmen, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Department Inventory, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Department Seminars, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Directory of Staff, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - E, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Economic Status of the Faculty Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - F, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - G, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Graduate School, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Griffin, Donald R., 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Hill, F. F., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - I, J, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - K, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Medical Student Accomplishment Report, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - N, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - O, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - P, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Parmenter, Richard, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Policy, Committee on University, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Positions at other institutions, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - President, Office of the, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Purchasing Department, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - R, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Recommendation, Letters of, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Summer Session, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - T, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - V, W, correspondents by last name, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Ward's Natural Science Establishment, Inc., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Will Corporation, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Willers, Diedrich K., 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Wright, T. P., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1953-1954
    - A, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Animals, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Assistantship, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Assistantship cont., 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Applications, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - B, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - C, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - D, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Da-Lite Screen Co., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Dean, Office of the, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - de Boom, H. P. A., 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Denoyer-Geppert Company, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Department Maintenance, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Department General Order, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Department Staff Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Department Inventory, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Department Seminars, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Directory of Staff, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - E, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Exchange of Persons Program, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - G, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Graduate School, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Graduate School Rejections, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Grant Applications, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Griffin, Donald R., 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Hill, F. F., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Hiring Teaching Assistants, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Hutton, James, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Higher Education, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - K, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - L, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Models, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - N, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - National Society for Medical Research, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - O, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - P, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Parmenter, Richard, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Phi Kappa Phi, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Positions at other institutions, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - President, Office of the, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Purchasing Department, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - R, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Recommendation, Letters of, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Retirement, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Sigma Xi, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Sound Motion Picture Projector, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Summer Session, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Selective Service, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Theses, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Veterinary School, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - W, correspondents by last name, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Ward's Natural Science Establishment, Inc., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Will Corporation, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Willers, Diedrich K., 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Wright, T. P., 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1954-1955
    - A, correspondents by last name, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Animal Room, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Assistantship, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Applications, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - C, correspondents by last name, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Dean, Office of the, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Distribution Requirements, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Department Chemical Order, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Department Inventory, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Department Seminars, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Department Staff Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Directory, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - E, correspondents by last name, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - F, correspondents by last name, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Film, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - G, correspondents by last name, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Graduate School, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Griffin, Donald R., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - I, J, correspondents by last name, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - K, correspondents by last name, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - L, correspondents by last name, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - Laboratory Furniture Company, Inc., 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - Maps, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - N, correspondence by last name, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - P, correspondents by last name, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - Position for Research, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - Personnel Office, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - Photo Science Service Bulletin, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - Positions at other institutions, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - President, Office of the, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - Provost, Office of the, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 134)
    - Public Information, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 135)
    - Purchasing Department, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 136)
    - R, correspondents by last name, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - Recommendation, Letters of, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 139)
    - Research Club, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - Selective Service, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - Singer, Marcus, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 143)
    - Statler Club, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 144)